A user starts in LexNordic, a private Swedish migration consultation workspace.
The workspace uses Supabase Auth, so sessions, chat history, matters, and files stay user-owned.
The user asks a normal migration question. They do not need to know the legal route first.
The answer streams while route, documents, sources, risks, and packet readiness are checked.
The default answer stays simple, but the proof layer reveals the Band-style specialist work trace.
The same conversation becomes a structured matter with route, evidence, source, and packet state.
The Route page compares permit paths, readiness, next questions, and current rule overlays.
Evidence requirements become actionable document tasks instead of scattered checklist notes.
Band collaboration is shown directly: pixel agents pass a shared case baton through the room.
The output is an AI case packet: checklist, next actions, source trail, and no automatic authority filing.
LexNordic turns migration uncertainty into a source-grounded, multi-agent consultation workflow.